Finding Aid for the Joe Menosky papers, 1983-2005, (bulk 1995-2001) LSC.2250
UCLA Library Special Collections
Joe Menosky papers
Bulk, 1995-2001
1983-2005
LSC.2250
UCLA Library Special Collections
17.8 linear feet (38 boxes, 2 cartons, and 1 flat box)
Joe Menosky is a writer, producer, and story editor who has worked in both television and film. He is best known for his work in science fiction, most notably the television series Star Trek Voyager. The bulk of collection consists of material for produced and unproduced television projects and motion pictures as well as items submitted to Menosky for consultation. Additionally included are articles by Menosky and a small amount of ephemera and publications related to the Star Trek franchise.
Menosky, Joe
Restrictions on Access
COLLECTION STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF: Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Joe Menosky, 2010.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 7769221
Biography/History
There is little biographical information available about Joe Menosky. Joe Menosky is a writer, producer, and story editor who has worked in both television and film. He is best known for his work in science fiction, most notably the television series Star Trek Voyager.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of material related to the career of story editor, writer, and producer, Joe Menosky. The collection includes script materials related to produced and unproduced motion picture and television projects, including items submitted to Menosky for consultation, articles written by Menosky, and a small quantity of publications and memorabilia related to the Star Trek franchise. Among the many projects represented are Anonymous Rex, Dead Like Me, Tomb Raider, Star Trek IX, Star Trek Resurrection, and Star Trek Voyager. A small amount of files and publications may have been assembled by production assistant, Michael O'Halloran
Organization and Arrangement
Arranged in the following series:
Television Projects
Motion Pictures Projects
Submissions to Menosky/Informal Consulting
Articles by Menosky
Publications and Memorabilia
Menosky, Joe -- Archives; Screenwriters--United States--Archives.; Television writers--United States--Archives.
- Television Projects, 1970s, 1990s-2004
  Scope and Content
  The television projects files contain complete and partial draft scripts, story outlines, series and story proposals, a small amount of production material. Among the projects in the series are Anonymous Rex, Dead Like Me, and Star Trek Voyager. Files are arranged alphabetically by project and file tiles.
  - Anonymous Rex cast and crew lists, (2004 March) (Box 31)
  - Anonymous Rex Dinosaurs An Illustrated Guide comic book, (undated) (Box 30)
  - Anonymous Rex Dinosaurs for Hire comic books, Issues 1-10, (undated) (Box 30)
  - Anonymous Rex Dinosaur prosthetic make-up photographs, (undated) (Box 30)
  - Anonymous Rex DK Dinosaurs Revealed by Dougal Dixon, (2003) (Box 31)
  - Anonymous Rex Guess Who's Coming for Basil - draft script, (undated) (Box 30)
  - Anonymous Rex handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 30)
    General note
    Also includes notes on Witch Hunter Robin
  - Anonymous Rex Hollywood Reporter review, (2004 Nov 29) (Box 31)
    Review of series on p. 73.
  - Anonymous Rex My First Book of Dinosaurs by Dougal Dixon, (2002) (Box 31)
  - Anonymous Rex Pilot episode - first draft script, (2001 May 18) (Box 31)
  - Anonymous Rex Pilot episode - revised story outline, (2003 July 14) (Box 31)
  - Anonymous Rex Pilot episode teleplay, (2004 Feb 2) (Box 31)
  - Anonymous Rex Scientific American Magazine - Special Edition: Dinosaurs and Other Monsters, (2004 June 21) (Box 31)
  - Anonymous Rex shooting schedules and scene shots, (2004 April) (Box 31)
  - Anonymous Rex A Detective Story - original novel by Eric Garcia, (2000) (Box 31)
  - Anonymous Rex baseball cap, (undated) (Box 6)
  - Anonymous Rex Hollywood Reporter article, (2004 Jan 24) (Box 31)
    News item on p. 4-5.
  - Anonymous Rex letter from Bruce Hutchinson to HR Canada Centre re: work authorization, (2004 Feb 24) (Box 31)
  - Anonymous Rex photograph of 2 actors in character, (undated) (Box 31)
  - Anonymous Rex pilot episode teleplay, (2004 April 12) (Box 31)
  - Anonymous Rex placard, (undated) (Box 39)
  - Chain (The) pilot episode - third draft script, (2001 Feb 16) (Box 16)
  - Colossus: Colossus and Collosus and the Crab - original novels by D.F. Jones, (1966/1977) (Box 32)
  - Colossus: Forbin Project (The) - DVD, (1970) (Box 33)
  - Colossus: The Fall of Colossus and Immortal Colossus novels by D.F. Jones and Douglas Perry, (1974/2000) (Box 32)
    Also includes handwritten notes
  - Dead Like Me: Dead Girl - first draft script, (undated) (Box 32)
    See also The Dead Zone.
  - Dead Like Me: Doggie Style - draft script, (undated) (Box 32)
  - Dead Like Me: handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 32)
  - Dead Like Me: handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 32)
  - Dead Like Me: handwritten notes and story proposals, (2001) (Box 32)
  - Dead Zone (The): 2001-2002 Season script status report, (2002 Aug 22) (Box 32)
    Produced as Dead Like Me.
  - Dead Zone (The): Enigma - handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 32)
  - Dead Zone (The): Finale - notes and commentaries, (2002 April 30) (Box 32)
  - Dead Zone (The): First Born - handwritten notes, (2002) (Box 32)
  - Dead Zone (The): Painting and Finale - handwritten notes, (2002) (Box 31)
  - Dead Zone (The): Shaman - handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 32)
  - Dead Zone (The): Zion - draft script, (undated) (Box 32)
  - Hercules correspondence and story outline, (1993 May 22) (Box 32)
  - P. A. written productions notes, (undated) (Box 38)
  - Paramount Pictures property removal notice, (undated) (Box 26)
    Document given to writers vacating their offices.
  - Photographs of Menosky, Jonathan Frakes as William Riker, and office, (ca. 1992) (Box 32)
  - Planetes series proposal, (undated) (Box 26)
  - Polonowski correspondence and postcards, (1998-2001) (Box 38)
    From infamous mentally ill Star Trek fan.
  - Star Trek fax letter from Patrick Stewart to Rick Berman (development letter), (1997 July 7) (Box 16)
  - Star Trek Deep Space Nine call sheets (Folder 1 of 2), (1995 Aug-Feb 1996) (Box 12)
  - Star Trek Deep Space Nine call sheets (Folder 2 of 2), (1995 Aug-Feb 1996) (Box 12)
  - Star Trek Deep Space Nine publicity still of cast - autographed (3 copies), (undated) (Box 22)
  - Star Trek Enterprise Tulsa - story outline, (2001 March 19) (Box 11)
  - Star Trek II - Writers/Directors Guide, (1977 Aug 12) (Box 15)
    Proposal for Star Trek Next Generation shared with Star Trek staff.
  - Star Trek The Next Generation: cast head shots autographed to Ryan, (undated) (Box 20)
  - Star Trek The Next Generation: Darmok - final draft script, (1991 July 8) (Box 18)
  - Star Trek The Next Generation: Darmok - first draft script, (1990 March 16) (Box 11)
  - Star Trek The Next Generation: Emergence - draft script and handwritten notes, (1994) (Box 30)
  - Star Trek The Next Generation: Masks - fan Letter to Menosky, (1994 March 3) (Box 30)
  - Star Trek The Next Generation: Masks - first draft script, (1993 Nov 29) (Box 30)
  - Star Trek The Next Generation: memo re: LaManna scenes in unidentified episode, (1996 April 2) (Box 7)
  - Star Trek The Next Generation: Writers'/Directors' Guide, fifth season edition, (1991 April) (Box 15)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Technical Guide V1.0, (undated) (Box 13)
  - Star Trek Voyager: 11:59 - story proposal, (1998 Nov 23) (Box 1)
  - Star Trek Voyager: airdate schedules, (1997 March 30) (Box 19)
  - [Star Trek Voyager?] artist renderings of ships, (undated) (Box 5)
  - Star Trek Voyager: artist sketches, (undated) (Box 39)
  - Star Trek Voyager: beat sheet for unidentified episode, (2001 Feb 7) (Box 13)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Bitter Pill - story proposal, (1998 June 11) (Box 1)
    Formerly known as Monster of the Deep.
  - Star Trek Voyager: Blink of an Eye - final draft script, (1999 Oct 13) (Box 13)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Blink of an Eye - final draft script, (1999 Oct 13) (Box 15)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Blink of an Eye - first draft story outline and first draft script, (1999 March, Sep, Dec) (Box 18)
    With memo to Writer's Guild.
  - Star Trek Voyager: Bliss - memo with commentary, (1998 Nov) (Box 5)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Borg Cube sketch, (1998 Nov 6) (Box 29)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Bride of Chaotica! - first draft script, (1998 Sep 30) (Box 1)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Broken Wing - episode commentaries, (1999 Nov 10) (Box 29)
  - Star Trek Voyager: call sheets, (1995 Aug-Dec) (Box 12)
  - Star Trek Voyager: call sheets, (1995 Oct-April 1996) (Box 12)
  - Star Trek Voyager: call sheets, (1997 Mar - July 1996) (Box 3)
  - Star Trek Voyager: call Sheets, (1997 May - Oct) (Box 2)
  - Star Trek Voyager: call Sheets, (1997 Oct - Jan 1998) (Box 2)
  - Star Trek Voyager: call sheets, (1998 April-July) (Box 21)
  - Star Trek Voyager: call sheets, (1998 Aug-Oct) (Box 21)
  - Star Trek Voyager: call sheets, (1998 Nov-March 1999) (Box 21)
  - Star Trek Voyager: call sheets, (1999 June-Aug) (Box 21)
  - Star Trek Voyager: call sheets, (1999 Sep-Dec) (Box 21)
  - Star Trek Voyager: call sheets, (2000 Dec-April 2001) (Box 12)
  - Star Trek Voyager: call sheets, (2000 Jan-April) (Box 21)
  - Star Trek Voyager: call sheets, (2000 June-Dec) (Box 12)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Caretaker - final draft script, (1994 Sep 1) (Box 18)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Caretaker (The) - final draft script, (1994 Sep 1) (Box 3)
  - Star Trek Voyager: cast lists, (1997 Jan-Feb 1998) (Box 19)
    For multiple episodes
  - Star Trek Voyager: character list, (1995 July 12) (Box 1)
  - Star Trek Voyager: character profiles, (undated) (Box 25)
  - Star Trek Voyager: correspondence and episode commentaries, (1996-1997) (Box 18)
  - Star Trek Voyager: correspondence on story ideas, (1996 May 21) (Box 9)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Critical Care - episode commentary, (2000 Aug 28) (Box 13)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Delirium - first draft script, (1997 June 9) (Box 25)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Destiny - script material, (2001 Feb 21) (Box 11)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Distant Origin - final draft script, (1997 Jan 23) (Box 29)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Distant Origin - memos re: script, (1997 March) (Box 2)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Distant Origin - scene shots, (undated) (Box 38)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Dragon's Teeth - script material, (1999 July 7) (Box 18)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Drone - script material, (1998 June 15) (Box 8)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Drone - script material, (1998 June 15) (Box 8)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Echoes of the Void - cassette tape, (undated) (Box 6)
  - Star Trek Voyager: editing notes for various episodes, (undated) (Box 11)
  - Star Trek Voyager: emails from Jamahl Epsicokhan to Bob Gillan re: The Jammer's review of Voyager episodes, (1997 Sep-Nov) (Box 25)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Endgame, Part One - first draft script, (2001 March 5) (Box 11)
  - Star Trek Voyager: episode status reports and production notes, (1997-2001) (Box 13)
  - Star Trek Voyager: episode synopses, (undated) (Box 2)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Episode Synopses #101 - #220 (Folder 1 of 2), (undated) (Box 13)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Episode Synopses #101 - #220 (Folder 2 of 2), (undated) (Box 13)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Fair Haven - final draft script, (1999 Sep 21) (Box 13)
  - Star Trek Voyager: False Idols - handwritten script material and beat sheet, (1996 Feb) (Box 29)
  - Star Trek Voyager: fifth season cast list and budget, (1998-1999) (Box 15)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Fight (The) - beat sheet, (1998 Oct 13) (Box 15)
  - Star Trek Voyager: final episode - handwritten notes and press kit, (2001 March) (Box 3)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Flashback - production information, (1996 Feb) (Box 7)
  - Star Trek Voyager: fourth season cast and crew list, (1997 May 27) (Box 19)
  - Star Trek Voyager: fourth season cast and crew list, (1998 Jan 15) (Box 18)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Future's End - draft script, (undated) (Box 19)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Future's End - draft script, (undated) (Box 19)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Future's End - first draft script, (1996 July 22) (Box 19)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Future's End - script material, (undated) (Box 17)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Future's End - story outline, (1996 July 3) (Box 5)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Future's End, Episodes I, II and III - story outlines and memos with commentary, (1996 June-July) (Box 7)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Future's End, Episodes I, II, and III - first draft story outline, (1996 June 28) (Box 19)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Gift (The) - first draft script, (1997 May 27) (Box 11)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Good Shepherd - draft script, story outline, and beat sheet, (1999 Dec-Jan 2000) (Box 29)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Good Shepherd - email correspondence, (1999 Dec 9) (Box 26)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Good Shepherd - final draft script, (2000 Jan 10) (Box 22)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Good Shepherd - final draft script, (2000 Jan 10) (Box 8)
    2 copies
  - Star Trek Voyager: Good Shepherd - handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 29)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Good Shepherd - story outline, (1999 Dec 9) (Box 13)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Ground Zero - handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 19)
  - [Star Trek Voyager?] handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 1)
  - Star Trek Voyager: handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 5)
  - Star Trek Voyager: handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 8)
  - Star Trek Voyager: handwritten notes, (undated) (Box 26)
  - Star Trek Voyager: handwritten notes and Harry Kloor Pitch, (1997) (Box 1)
  - Star Trek Voyager: handwritten notes for Borg episodes, (undated) (Box 29)
  - Star Trek Voyager: handwritten story notes, (undated) (Box 29)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Hope and Fear - draft script, sample artist sketches, and blue prints, (1998 Feb) (Box 29)
  - Star Trek Voyager: In the Flesh - final draft script, (1998 July 1) (Box 11)
  - Star Trek Voyager: In the Flesh - first draft script, (1998 June 15) (Box 11)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Infinite Regress - script material, (1998 Aug 18) (Box 11)
  - Star Trek Voyager: invitation to end-of-6th-season party at the Derby, (2000 March 29) (Box 26)
  - Star Trek Voyager: invitation to end-of-season party at El Cholo Restaurant, (1997) (Box 26)
  - Star Trek Voyager: invitation to Menosky for showing of final episode, (2001 April 11) (Box 15)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Janeway novel - story outline, (undated) (Box 20)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Keep (The) - story outline, (undated) (Box 13)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Latent Image - first draft script, (1998 Sep 21) (Box 18)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Latent Image - first draft script and script material, (1998 Sep) (Box 9)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Latent Image - first draft story outline, (1998 Sep 18) (Box 14)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Latent Image - script material, (1998 Sep 30) (Box 9)
  - Star Trek Voyager: legal correspondence, (1998 Nov-Dec) (Box 29)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Little Prince (The) - story proposal, (1999 Nov 22) (Box 29)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Living Witness - draft script, (undated) (Box 25)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Living Witness - final draft script, (1998 Jan 26) (Box 29)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Living Witness - first draft script, (1998 Jan 19) (Box 11)
  - Star Trek Voyager: make up and costume polaroids, (undated) (Box 38)
  - Star Trek Voyager: make up and costume polaroids, (undated) (Box 38)
  - Star Trek Voyager: memo from Menosky to Braga regarding Archive (possible unproduced story proposal), (2001 April 17) (Box 29)
  - Star Trek Voyager: memo regardimg script covers submissions for approval, (1998 May 29) (Box 19)
  - Star Trek Voyager: memo regarding Jeri Ryan publicity campaign, (1997 June 3) (Box 19)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Memoria - handwritten story proposal, (undated) (Box 29)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Memorial - final draft story outline, (1999 Oct 8) (Box 14)
  - Star Trek Voyager: memos re: episode teleplays, (1996-1998) (Box 5)
  - Star Trek Voyager: memos re: episode teleplays, (1998 May-July) (Box 7)
  - Star Trek Voyager: memos re: episode teleplays, (1998-1999) (Box 5)
  - Star Trek Voyager: memos regarding budget trims, (2001 March 31) (Box 22)
    May also relate to Star Trek Deep Space Nine.
  - Star Trek Voyager: memos regarding network ratings for August 28, 1995 and viewer research questionaire, (1995 Aug 29) (Box 19)
  - Star Trek Voyager: memos with script status reports, (1996 Aug-Feb 1997) (Box 2)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Message in a Bottle - character list, (undated) (Box 1)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Monsters - story proposal, (2000 Jan 4) (Box 29)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Muse - call sheet, (2000 March 1) (Box 8)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Muse - correspondence, (2000 Feb 15) (Box 8)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Muse - correspondence, notes, and script material, (undated) (Box 1)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Muse - final draft script, (2000 Feb 24) (Box 19)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Muse - final draft script, (2000 Feb 24) (Box 11)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Muse - final draft script, (2000 Feb 24) (Box 26)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Muse - final draft script, (2000 Feb 24) (Box 29)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Muse - final draft script, (2000 Feb 24) (Box 19)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Muse - final draft script, (2000 Feb 24) (Box 8)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Muse - first draft script, (2000 Feb 14) (Box 13)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Muse - first draft script, (2000 Feb 14) (Box 8)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Muse - first draft script, (2000 Reb 14) (Box 26)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Muse - first draft script (Folder 1 of 2), (2000 Feb 14) (Box 7)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Muse - first draft script (Folder 2 of 2), (2000 Feb 24) (Box 7)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Muse - first draft script and script material (Folder 1 of 2), (2000 Feb 24) (Box 9)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Muse - first draft script and script material (Folder 2 of 2), (2000 Feb 14) (Box 9)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Muse - first draft script and story outline, (2000 Feb) (Box 18)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Muse - first draft story outline, (2000 Jan 31) (Box 19)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Muse - first draft story outline and correspondence, (2000 Jan) (Box 13)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Muse - handwritten notes and story outline, (undated) (Box 1)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Muse - production information, (2000 Feb) (Box 9)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Muse - production notes, (2000 Feb) (Box 8)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Muse - script material, (2000 Feb) (Box 15)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Muse - script material, (2000 Feb) (Box 9)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Muse - script material, (2000 Feb 29) (Box 8)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Muse - script material, (2000 Feb 29) (Box 8)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Muse - script material and handwritten notes, (2000 Feb 25) (Box 18)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Muse - script material and notes, (2000) (Box 15)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Muse - shooting schedule, (2000 March 1) (Box 26)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Muse - story outline, production schedule, notes, (2000 Jan 31) (Box 8)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Muse - story proposal, (2000 Jan 25) (Box 18)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Natural Law - memo with commentary, (2001 Feb 2) (Box 1)
  - Star Trek Voyager: newspaper clippings, (1997-1998) (Box 15)
  - Star Trek Voyager: No Gods Before Me - story proposal, (1999 May 18) (Box 1)
  - Star Trek Voyager: No Gods Before Me - story proposal and handwritten notes, (1999 June 7) (Box 1)
  - Star Trek Voyager: No Place Like Home - script, (undated) (Box 11)
  - Star Trek Voyager: notes and crew list, (1996) (Box 7)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Nothing Human - memo re: sound editing, (1998 Sep 15) (Box 7)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Once Upon a Database - story proposal, (1996 Oct 17) (Box 18)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Once Upon a Database? - story proposal, (1996 Oct 17) (Box 29)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Once Upon a Time - revised beat sheet, (1998 July 5) (Box 29)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Ondron Massacre (The) - preliminary draft story outline, (1999 Oct 7) (Box 14)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Origin of Species (The) - story outline, (2000 Jan 11) (Box 26)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Paradigm - fourth draft story outline, (1996 May 31) (Box 9)
  - Star Trek Voyager: party invitations, (1998-2001) (Box 13)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Perfect Mission (The) - story synopsis, (undated) (Box 1)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Photons Be Free - story outline, (undated) (Box 25)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Photons Be Free! - story outline, (undated) (Box 7)
  - Star Trek Voyager: plaque - Fifth Season, (undated) (Box 40)
  - Star Trek Voyager: plaque - Fourth Season, (undated) (Box 40)
  - Star Trek Voyager: plaque - Second Season, (undated) (Box 40)
  - Star Trek Voyager: plaque - Sixth Season, (1999 Dec) (Box 40)
  - Star Trek Voyager: plaque - Third Season, (undated) (Box 40)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Scheherzade - preliminary story outline, (1998 April 23) (Box 18)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Scorpion - final draft script, (1997 Feb 26) (Box 30)
    `
  - Star Trek Voyager: Scorpion, Part 2 - first draft script, (1997 May 14) (Box 7)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Scorpion, Part II - final draft script, (1997 May 23) (Box 30)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Scorpion, Part II - notes, memos, and script material, (1997) (Box 2)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Scorpion, Part Two - first draft script and script material, (1997 May 14) (Box 9)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Scorpion, Part Two - script, (1997 May 5) (Box 2)
    First draft
  - Star Trek Voyager: Scorption, Part 2 - first draft script, (1997 May 5) (Box 7)
  - Star Trek Voyager: script notes on unidentified episodes, (undated) (Box 5)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Season 6 director's schedule, (1999 March 8) (Box 29)
  - Star Trek Voyager: season 6 script status report, (2000 March 20) (Box 26)
  - Star Trek Voyager: season 6 script status report, (2000 March 7) (Box 26)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Season Four Finale - story outline, (1998 Feb) (Box 1)
  - Star Trek Voyager: season Seven Finale - notes and story outlines, (2000) (Box 13)
  - Star Trek Voyager: series maintenance, (1998 Feb) (Box 7)
  - Star Trek Voyager: series maintenance information, (1996 March) (Box 19)
  - Star Trek Voyager: series maintenance questionnaire, (1998 March 17) (Box 21)
  - Star Trek Voyager: series outline and bible, (1994-1995) (Box 2)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Siren - story proposal, (1996 Aug 19) (Box 19)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Spirit Folk - final draft script, (1999 Nov 29) (Box 11)
  - Star Trek Voyager: story ideas, (1998-1999) (Box 9)
  - Star Trek Voyager: tech photographs, (undated) (Box 38)
  - Star Trek Voyager: technical Manual, (undated) (Box 13)
  - Star Trek Voyager: technical notes and artist renderings, (1994-1995) (Box 2)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Thaw (The) - final draft script, (1996 Jan 19) (Box 29)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Timeless - memos re: sound editing, (1998 Sep) (Box 7)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Tinker Tenor Doctor Spy - final draft script, (1999 July 9) (Box 18)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Tinker Tenor Doctor Spy - final draft script, (1999 July 9) (Box 20)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Tinker Tenor Doctor Spy - final draft script, (1999 July 9) (Box 15)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Tinker Tenor Doctor Spy - final draft script, (1999 July 9) (Box 29)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Tinker Tenor Doctor Spy - first draft script, (1999 June 29) (Box 13)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Tinker Tenor Doctor Spy - first draft script, (1999 June 29) (Box 20)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Tinker Tenor Doctor Spy - first draft script, (1999 June 29) (Box 15)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Tinker Tenor Doctor Spy - first draft script, (1999 June 29) (Box 14)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Tinker Tenor Doctor Spy - first draft story outline, (1999 June 8) (Box 11)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Tinker Tenor Doctor Spy - Menosky employment contract, (1999 June 30) (Box 2)
  - Star Trek Voyager: Tinker Tenor Doctor Spy - notes, shooting schedules, and musical scores, (1999 July-Aug) (Box 20)